# **SACHIN KUMAR**

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Team Leader experienced in directing activities of workgroups. Develops strategies, provides training, sets goals and obtains team feedback. Excellent interpersonal and communication skills. Big picture focus with excellence in communicating goals and vision to succeed. Problem solver, networker and consensus builder.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

## Team Leader, 07/2021 to Current IEnergizer - Noida , India

- 1
- Ienerziger sector 60 noida (Make my trip), Subway reach airia mall Gurgaon sector 68
- Built strong relationships with customers through positive attitude and attentive response.
- Facilitated training for associates through daily coaching and regular performance appraisals.
- · Supported office business development and customer service.
- Assisted with new hire processing and existing training programs.
- Led team of Number members while providing exceptional customer service.
- Worked with colleagues to create prototypes for designs and training materials.
- Optimized customer support by establishing collaborative service environments through targeted operational initiatives.

# Shift Manager, 09/2020 to 04/2021

#### Subway - Gurgaon, India

- Excelled in every store position and regularly backed up front-line staff.
- · Trained and mentored new employees to maximize team performance.
- Managed schedules, accepted time off requests and found coverage for short shifts.
- Kept employees operating productively and working on task to meet business and customer needs.
- Worked closely with team members to schedule breaks and shifts to meet state regulations.
- Adhered to company standards and compliance requirements for operations and cleanliness of areas.

#### CONTACT

Address: Noida, India 201301

**Phone:** +917351811582, +917351811582 **Email:** sachinjadaun3322@gmail.com

**WWW:** Bold Profile

#### SKILLS

- · Coaching and Mentoring
- · Staff Training
- Continuous Professional Improvement
- Verbal and Written Communication
- · Work Planning and Prioritization
- · Shift Scheduling
- People Management
- · Shift Checklists

#### Nicsmann 1940 - Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- · Cell: +60 17-298 9361
- · E-mail: hello@friendscino.com
- Job Description
- · Providing excellent wait service to ensure satisfaction
- Taking customer orders and delivering food and beverages
- Making menu recommendations, multi-tasking various frontof-the-house duties and collecting the bill.
- Created successful work schedules for each team member to maintain deadlines and fully staff shifts.
- Worked with management team to implement proper division of responsibilities.
- Identified individual employee's unique work styles and adapted management methods.
- Tracked and prepared quarterly reports to present to leadership.

# F&B Associate, 07/2017 to 06/2018 Kridha Residency - Vrindavan, India

- 91 565 254 0151
- · E-mail: resturant@kridharesidency.com
- Job Description
- · Presenting a variety of menu options
- Advising on the best food and drink choices for each customer and answering questions
- Check with customers to ensure that they are enjoying their meals and take action to correct any problems
- 5.
- Greeted guests at front desk and engaged in pleasant conversations while managing check-in process.
- Resolved customer issues quickly and notified supervisor immediately when problems escalated.

### Vocational Trainee, 04/2017 to 06/2017 Ramada Udaipur Resort - Vrindavan, India

- Managed communication between program applicants and staff.
- · Kept facilities clean, neat and organized for professional appeal.
- Developed and implemented lesson plans for classes or sessions in support of senior staff members.
- · Performed initial screenings and applicant intake.

#### **EDUCATION**

Diploma, Hotel Management, 2017

Impulse Institute of Management, Hotel Management - Arga, India

Contact No: +91 72482 45774 E-mail: info@iimworld.com

Certificate of Continuous and Comprehensive Evaluation, 2016 U.P BOARD RAMJI LAL HSS DHIMSHRI FATEHABAD - AGRA, INDIA

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Personal Dossier Name: Sachin Kumar Father's Name: MR. Radhe Shyam

Mother's Name: Mrs. Guddi Devi Date of Birth: 07 May 2000